Dawn- Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre,

Princes Town.

Tel: (868) 469-6292/655-1316. **Email:** dmarthamc@outlook.com

10th August, 2017

To Whom It May Concern.

Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am applying for the available position of **CSR/ Cashier** within the organization.

Over the years I have worked in various positions, including voluntary ones as you would see in my attached CV. I view every working and volunteering opportunity as a learning tool used in my development by challenging myself to become the best steward over the responsibilities assigned to me. Additionally, I am always willing to learn to be more effective in such. It is not always easy, but that's where I believe growth comes.

In closing, I do look forward to an interview with you at your convenience and hope that you view me as a suitable candidate for hire.

Thanking you in advance.

Yours respectfully,

.....

Mrs. Dawn McLeod. (Applicant)

Curriculum Vitae

Dawn-Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre, Princes Town. Contact: (868) 469-6292

Email: dmarthamc@outlook.com

Work Experience

July 2015- June 2016

Revival Fire

Administrative Assistant (Voluntary)

Contact: 225-7286/726-5601

Duties: General Administrative Duties.

Feb. 2014 – Current.

TFRS Tiling Fabricating and Renovation Services.

Business Partner

Contact: 356-5549/ 375-0727

Duties: General Administrative and Customer Service Duties, Strategic Planning/

Marketing and Payroll.

Dec. 2013 – Feb. 2014

LSC Tutoring

(Worked From Home)

Service Coordinator Contact: 330-8341

Duties: Plan and Coordinate organization's events and workshops, Customer Service,

Timesheets and Payroll, Basic Graphic Designs for flyers etc. and Marketing.

2010 and 2012

Daniel Johnson Scaffolding

Point Fortin

Executive Assistant

Contact: 722-0329/ 334-1054

Duties: General administrative duties, Time sheets and Payroll including Banking Duties, Supervise workers, Customer Service, Errands for Executives, Receptionist Duties etc.

2011

Youth for Christ

Barataria

Technical/ Graphic Assistant (Studio)

Contact: 674-3931

Work Experience Continued.

2010

Anthony Henry and Associates Co. Ltd.

Chaguanas

Human Resource Coordinator

Contact: 733-0038

Duties: Assist Executives in the hiring and firing process based on the Human Resource regulations of the organization governed by Law, Timesheets, Payroll, Develop Policies and Procedures for company, Report writing, Performance Appraisals, Errands, Motivational Incentives etc.

2006-2009

2000-2001

Various Entry Level Jobs (Cashier, Receptionist, Voluntary services, etc.)

Qualifications

| 2010- 2013 | Advanced Christian Training Seminars Certificate in Ministry |
|------------|--|
| 2007 | School of Business and Computer Science (SBCS) Certificate (Introductory) Human Resource Management |
| 2003-2004 | Youth Training and Employment Partnership Program Certificate Level 1 Hairdressing |

Junior Achievement of Trinidad and Tobago

Education

Junior Achiever

| 2006 | Private Candidate | General Proficiency | | |
|--------------------------|----------------------------|----------------------------|-----|--|
| Human and Social Biology | | Grade III | (3) | |
| | | | | |
| 2003-2004 | Private Candidate | | | |
| Mathematics | | Grade III | (3) | |
| | | | | |
| 2002-2003 | Bishops' Centenary College | | | |
| English A | | Grade II | (2) | |
| Food & Nutrition | | Grade II | (2) | |
| Social-Studies ` | | Grade III | (3) | |

Education Continued

1997-2001 Providence Girls RC Secondary School

1995-1997 St. Joseph Girls RC School

Personal Information

Date of Birth: 13th April 1985

Marital Status: Married

Gender: Female

References

Ms. Savita Beharry

Purchasing Manager California Stucco Co. Ltd. #2 Harridass St Warner Vge.

Charlieville.

Contact: 671-0358/391-3706

Mr. Brent Pedro

Founder/ Apostle Revival Fire Apostolic Centre

Office: 225-7286 Cell: 492-1374